First of all, enter the default clothing version, drag it out to the straight line point, adjust the version, press the Alt key, click to drag it out to the outside of the screen, you can use the AI curve tool
Adjust the side of the clothing, widen the overall width of the clothing
Due to the adjustment of the width of the clothing, we still need to ensure that the length of the sleeve is the same
When we adjust the straight line point, press the Shift key to use the guide line
We can also adjust its curve point
When adjusting the straight line point, click on the right button, you can enter the value in the window
Extend the sleeve version
After extending, rearrange the version
Solve the gap
Use the change length tool to modify the length of the sleeve
When modifying, you can change the direction
Use the internal line tool to create the internal line
Cut and sew the internal line to make the sleeve
You can arrange the straight line point
Adjust the size of the sleeve
Use the internal line tool and expand the outer line of the version to create the internal line
In the 3D window, adjust the position of the version
Clear the original sewing line
Then use the free sewing tool to sew the lower part of the clothing
This can ensure that the opening has an open effect
Next, click on the outer line of the version to measure the length of the collar
Use the multidirectional tool to create an equal length of the version
Align the version, then arrange the version around the virtual model
Use the free sewing tool to sew
When sewing, click on the Shift key
You can do the most one-to-one sewing
Sew the back of the collar
We need to adjust the shape of the collar
When making the collar, it is necessary to ensure that the curve of the collar plate
Can correspond to the curve of the collar
Click on the Alt key to adjust the curve
At the same time, it is necessary to ensure that the four corners of the plate are straight
This can make the part of the collar more flat
Adjust the length of the collar and adjust the curve
To match the curve of the collar
Click on the outer line of the version of the collar to measure the length
And create an equal length of the version as the collar
You can align the version to the opening edge
Adjust the curve of the collar
Let it correspond to the curve of the collar
At the same time, keep the four corners straight
Because the length of the collar has been adjusted
We still need to reaffirm whether they are equal in length
Use the free sewing tool to sew
After choosing the version, you can add it to the outside
Add again, you can fold the collar down
Lower the particle diameter to make the collar smoother
Use the free sewing tool to add the corner of the collar
And at the same time reduce the vertical angle of the collar
Make the width of the plate smoother
Next, add the button
After the button is heavy, click on the plate to add
When the cloth is attached, click on the right click
You can fold it in the same way
Adjust the width of the collar
The size of the button down
For the button button
Awesome
Ask one of my friends to give a picture
There is the three buttons
First, you can turn the button by pushing and insert the button
Press the button back
Then connect the button
Then
The button is in the desired position
Right click
Press the right mouse button
You can see it
There is an differential button
It is快速就能移 desta轨
Vertical tab
Follow the position of theremoving button
You will find the button
Oh, I learned it
Theera is also connected to the steering wheel
To measure the length of the waist, then use the left-hand tool to create a belt plate with a 2D button and a button, and then arrange it around the model.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the front, back, and middle, and then use the right-hand sewing tool to sew the belt and pants plates.
We need to adjust the belt plate. First, I will merge it in the back, and then adjust its curve to match the curve of the pants plate.
Adjust the curve point on the pants to make it wider.
Use the inner line sewing tool to sew the inner line in the pants.
Freeze the belt plate. The frozen plate will not be involved in the simulation, but it still has a transparent effect.
Lower the pants to make the pants stand up.
Choose the inner line, then sew it.
Make the pants.
Re-activate the upper part of the pants, so that it is not involved in the transparent and simulation, and then reduce the pants plate.
Activate the pants plate.
The entire model is finished.
Use the
Then use the 3D drawing tool to draw the lines at the inner part of the door.
When you draw, press the save button to add the curve point.
Select the line section and turn it into the inner line
Align the inner line to the panel line and add points
Then use the hook tool to hook the panel line
Sew the panel line and the pants panel and change the sewing line type to TURN
TURN is two panels folded and sewed together
Cut Mangle is for sewing, sew two panels together
After arranging the position of the panel, simulate
Remove the sewing line in front of the pants until the bottom of the sewing line
Remove the sewing line in front of the belt and untie the belt
Fold the panel line to the other side
Use the panel line expansion to extend the belt panel
And the extended part is sewn in the Mangle part
Sew the front of the belt
Use the panel line extension to set the inner line on the other side
And the belt panel line is sewn on the inner line
This can fix the belt
Choose the Mangle panel and set the inner line
Sew the inner line of the Mangle
This can seal the Mangle part
In the simulation process, you can see that the Mangle panel line is sewn in the inner line of the Mangle panel.
You can turn the Mangle panel up and down manually
Choose the belt panel
Use the Mangle panel to slide down
Use the 3D drawing tool to draw the pocket
Press the CURVING button to add the curve point
Use the edit dot tool in the 3D window
Cut the Mangle panel
Use the panel line expansion to expand the pocket panel
Use the free sewing tool to sew the expansion part and the pants together
The pants are sewn together
The insoles are like a curve
Choose the Mangle panel and set the layer to the inside
The Mangle panel is automatically
built in
Next, we're going to make the panel
Use the free sewing tool to draw the panel
First, set the Mangle panel around the model
Then fold it
Adjust the Mangle panel from the 3D window before modeling
Fill in the blank space
Then use the free sewing tool to sew the waistband and waistband
When sewing, we can use the blue dots in the 3D window to locate
Because the version is too small, we can use the camera to adjust the particle diameter to make it have more network
Adjust the position of the pants
We can use the edit horizontal line tool to adjust the position of the pants horizontal
Select the outside line of the waistband and use the internal line ruler to set the internal line
Then use the multilayer tool
Set the position of an internal line and a long panel
Select the excess internal line and put it on the internal line of the waistband
Then use the free sewing tool to sew the waistband panel and internal line
After sewing, we select the panel and add it to the outside
After setting the result, scan the model to prevent conflict between the panels
Set the front and middle parts
This can save a waistband step
Select the panel line in the pocket position and set the internal line ruler
Then put the pocket on the internal line
This can prevent the pocket from overlapping with the outer panel
After finishing the clothing, adjust the panel to zero
In order to prevent conflicts between unnecessary panels in the later simulation process
Turn on the pants panel so that it is not involved in the conflict and simulation
Activate the top and bottom panels and reduce its tail rate
Make it close to the virtual model
Activate the pants panel and wear it
Set the level for the pants panel
Make it simulate the outer layer and freeze the top and bottom panels for simulation
Freeze the pants panel and activate the top and bottom panels
At the same time, adjust its tail rate to 100
Simulate again and you can see the difference in the fold
Select all panels
After setting all the panels, adjust the level to zero
To prevent conflicts between unnecessary panels
You can delete the invisible twist
Check the seam line
Change the seam line to Turn
Adjust the color of the pants panel
Adjust the material of the pants panel
The material used here is Carbon Garbage
Use this material to create larger folds
Because of the length of the panel
If the panel is too long, select the panel line, use the panel line expansion, change the expansion to narrow, shorten the panel.
Re-activate the panel outside the leg, adjust the length of the leg panel, and adjust its position during the modeling process.
Select the panel line in the seam part and apply elasticity, set the elasticity to 100, maintain the original line length.
Freeze the leg panel and activate the other panels.
In order to prevent the belt part from sliding down, you can freeze the belt and then simulate it.
Next, make the leg part.
In the 2D window, click the right button to add a background image.
In the drawing, you can change the shoes for the virtual model.
You can also change the color of the shoes.
Next, use a multidirectional model.
Use the multidirectional tool to draw the outline of the legs of the virtual model on the background image.
When drawing, we can click the control button to add a curve point.
Adjust the curve point on the panel.
Arrange the adjusted panel on the virtual model's legs.
When arranging, you can also change the shape of the model's heart to a flat surface.
Freeze the upper clothes and pants panels to prevent them from being simulated.
Before that, I will freeze this panel first.
Then I will create a small panel.
In the 3D window, I will adjust the position of the panel to make it as close to the ground as possible.
Then click the right button on the blank to select the simulation model.
In the model editor, I can adjust the height of the ground.
After modeling, you can observe that this panel can be based on the grid of the ground.
The made legs are too close to the ground.
In order to avoid conflict between the legs and the ground, it is necessary to reduce the height of the ground.
Align the panel, the panel and the sewing line.
Then activate the panel.
Sew the front, back and center.
Place a small panel and use the positioning tool to align the bottom part.
Since the panel is too short, I will make the panel longer.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the part of the leg and then simulate.
After the simulation, you will find that the panel of the leg can not be turned up.
This is because the panel of the pants is frozen.
The panel of the frozen panel will still have conflicts.
We need to activate it.
Once again, we can manually adjust the shape of the leg.
Turn the leg up.
Adjust the position of the straight point.
And make a long panel.
After arranging, use the sewing tool to sew from the part of the straight point.
You can shrink the leg by adjusting the length of this panel.
After copying and pasting a panel, continue to sew using the sewing tool.
The straight point added to the panel can help me to locate the position when sewing.
The leg of the pants has a corner.
We can adjust the straight point of the panel to make this part smoother.
Since the straight point of the panel is too large, it will have conflicts with the virtual model.
So we need to reduce the straight point of the panel.
After choosing the leg, apply a new fabric for it.
Change the fabric to a harder leather fabric.
After the fine wrinkles disappear, we can observe and adjust it in the 3D window.
Next, we need to reduce the surface diameter of the shoes and the virtual model.
After reducing the surface diameter, the gap between the virtual model and the panel will be smaller.
If you are making a relatively close-fitting outfit, then you must reduce the surface diameter and the thickness of the panel.
Use the internal multilayer tool to draw the internal line on the panel.
After choosing the internal line, we can also set the internal line diameter.
You can display or hide the internal line in the 3D window.
Align the internal line to the outer line of the panel and cut and sew the internal line.
Select the outer line of the panel in the front part of the leg and set the internal line diameter.
Use the internal line tool to click the panel.
In the 3D window, you can adjust the size and position of the circle.
On the other side, add the internal circle.
After selecting the internal circle, paste it.
When pasting, click the right button.
You can set the number in the 3D window.
Double-click to select a panel line on the panel.
Double-click again to select all panel lines.
After selecting, cut and sew it.
After cutting, rearrange the panel in the position in the 2D window.
Select the panel cut out.
The notice is that the circle of the circle and the shape of the circle are different.
Now, while preparing the displaying on the left side of the panel,
adjust the suitable position to make soil.
Select the curve point and right-click to remove the curve point.
Due to the large gap at the bottom, we can shorten the sheet.
Measure the length of the outline of the sheet.
Use a multidirectional tool to draw the shape of the sheet along the shape of the front of the leg.
When drawing, press the Ctrl key to add a curve point.
Draw only half of the sheet.
Open the edge of the sheet and apply the fabric to it.
Adjust the curve point on the sheet and adjust the shape of the sheet.
Due to the length of the outline of the sheet is not uniform, so I make this sheet longer.
Use a circular curve tool to add a corner.
Adjust the curve point to make the bottom as smooth as possible.
Arrange the sheet around the model.
You can see that the outline of the sheet now has a slightly curved shape.
Adjust the curve point to make it smoother.
Use a free sewing tool to sew this piece of sheet on the inside of the leg.
Freeze the leg sheet.
For this piece of sheet and the leg of the pants, set the level and let it be simulated to the innermost layer.
After the simulation is stable, adjust the level to 0.
Then activate the whole and simulate to see if it is stable.
Adjust the curve point to make it smooth.
Next, I will make a line on the side.
After making a long strip of sheet, arrange it on the leg of the virtual model.
Adjust the length of this piece of sheet.
Arrange the curve point .
on the table setting, we can change the positioning of the ball into a screen.
Using a screen can help us to adjust its position in the 3D window.
Then, use a free sewing tool to stitch the corner.
Use a free sewing tool to stitch the corner.
You can adjust the position of the sewing line by using the Edit Sewing Line tool.
After switching to grid mode, we will find that its vertical diameter is too large.
We need to reduce its vertical diameter to make it have more grid and become more round.
Copy and paste the line of this knot.
After arranging, continue to sew.
All the remaining knots are directly copied and pasted and then sewed.
Thank you for watching.
After the one side is finished, we directly select all the knots and press D to face the other side.
Switch the positioning ball to the screen coordinate and then move the board to the right position.
Then simulate.
I want to make the leg of the leg hanger completely cover the leg hanger.
So, I extend the length of the leg hanger.
As the length of the leg hanger has been adjusted, the middle leg hanger is a little stretched.
We need to adjust its sewing line.
If the leg hanger is a little longer than the length of the leg hanger,
We need to remove it first to be able to do the opposite.
After removing all the leg plates in the circle, remove the joint, and then align the plates.
Use the positioning ball to adjust the aligned plates to the right position and then simulate.
In order to avoid the leg from falling down during the simulation process, I will sew up the leg and the leg.
Use the MN free sewing tool to sew up the leg and the leg.
Use the MN free sewing tool to press the Enter key to complete the first sewing line creation.
Then continue to create the second sewing line.
Press the Enter key to complete the second sewing line creation.
Use the MN free sewing tool to shape the Viking and see if it is stable.
At this point, we still need to turn the sewing line type of the emblem.
This video is based on my own personal experience, I don't know if it's appropriate for you to watch this video or not.
Activate the pants panel, and then do the simulation layer by layer to see if the suit is stable. If the suit is not stable, it needs to be adjusted immediately.
Activate the pants panel, and then do the simulation layer together to solve the hole problem.
The level of set to-1 is to ensure that the pants are simulated in the innermost layer.
The level of set to-2 is to make sure that the suit is stable.
Here is the tutorial to apply the wool fabric to the suit.
The wool fabric can be used to add some more damage to the suit in order to make the suit more detailed.
Select the suit panel and hold down the vertical arrow to make it more detailed.
The suit panel can be used to add more damage to the suit.
After measuring the length of the inner line, I lengthened this board a little bit to cover the leg.
After lengthening the board, we need to adjust the sewing line.
In order to avoid an unstable process, I will first freeze the leg boards and then measure them.
After that, I will activate them.
After lengthening the boards, the excess fabric of the leg can still be sealed and the part of the leg can be removed.
Then I will measure them layer by layer.
This can ensure that the modeling costume is more stable.
We can set the level for the outer belt and the waistband to be simulated in the outer layer.
Activate the leg board and simulate to see if it is stable.
Then adjust the level of all the costumes to 0.
At this point, I will reduce the thickness of the fabric and the thickness of the seam allowance between them to make the gap between them smaller.
Reduce the thickness of the fabric.
When reducing the thickness of the fabric to 10, you can also reduce the thickness of the seam allowance to 1.
Then adjust the height of the leg to the right size and the seam allowance to 2.
We also reduce the part of the leg to the height of this cardigan and the other part to the height of the bag.
Then we reduce the length of the leg to a little bit shorter.
Then we can make the leg better in the range.
Finally, we can make the leg stronger.
In the side area, you can see the effect of God-striking board.
This place is a bit tight.
We can select the God-striking board and increase its tail-shape.
Then the model can be seen in this part will be more loose.
Freeze all the boards.
Next, we will make the jacket.
Select the shirt board and paste it.
We will make changes through this board.
First, we delete the internal line above and the decoder.
Then arrange it around the virtual model.
After arranging, set the level for the costume.
And increase its tail-shape.
Let it be simulated to the outer layer.
When modeling, we can give it a harder fabric.
For example, the leather fabric.
This can quickly eliminate the crumbling feet.
After completely modeling to the outer layer.
Adjust its tail-shape and level to the original value.
Then I will cut its fabric into Titan Guardian.
The same fabric as the pants.
We can reverse-activate.
No need to participate in the simulation and simulation of the board.
We can select the straight line on the board.
Turn it into a curve.
We can also select the straight line.
Delete the straight line.
Turn it into a straight line.
This part, I mainly adjust the shape of the costume.
Select the bottom white of the costume.
After the outline of the board.
We can directly add the board.
Use the plus point division tool.
Add a straight line to the waist of the costume.
When adding, on the board.
Click the right button.
You can enter the number in the spring.
After selecting the straight line of the front and back pieces.
I will shrink the waist.
Then ensure that the part of the sleeve is the right corner.
Adjust the straight line of the bottom white part.
When moving the straight line, click the right button.
We can enter the distance of movement in the spring.
Delete the sleeve board.
And adjust the length of the sleeve.
When adding, you can click the right button.
Enter the number.
Next, we are going to deal with the collar of the costume.
First, reverse-activate the collar.
Then I will use the internal multidirectional tool.
Modify the internal line.
We can arrange the position of the board in the 2D window first.
Let the board connect to each other.
There is enough space on the board.
Then we select the internal line.
We can align it with the outer line of the board.
Turn the vertical line point into a curve line point.
Then select the internal line.
Apply a angle of 180 degrees for it.
Then reverse-activate the board.
We will modify the board after hardening.
If the angle of the fold is affected.
The board will automatically fold down.
After selecting the curve line.
Delete all curve points.
Then in this area.
We can adjust the size of the collar.
After the collar is folded.
We can remove the hardening.
Activate the collar board.
After activating the collar board.
We will find.
Now its sewing line is not correct.
We need to adjust its sewing line position.
Use the edge sewing line tool to adjust.
Then we will find.
There is a part of the collar part.
We need to adjust it.
We need to delete the excess part.
Before deleting.
We will join the back of the seat.
After selecting the sewing line.
We can join.
Use the edge sewing line tool.
After selecting the sewing line.
We can add points at the starting point of the sewing line.
Then I will use the edge sewing line tool.
Start from this point.
Enter the edge line.
Then we can see the inner line.
After it is finished.
I will cut off the inner line.
Then delete the part of the lining.
In the collar part.
Do the same.
We activate the collar first.
Then we will measure the length of the seat and the current length of the seat.
Use the expansion of the panel line.
Change the expansion to shrink and modify the length of the seat.
And use the editor sewing line tool to adjust the position of the sewing line.
Adjust its curve to make it smoother.
And make the seat bigger and wider.
In order to ensure that it is more stable during the simulation process,
we will first set the unnecessary panel line.
Then adjust the panel line of the seat separately.
At this point, I will sew the front and rear panel lines together.
Use the free sewing tool to sew.
You can check the position of the sewing line in the 3D window.
After sewing the front and rear panel lines together, the front and rear panel lines will be more complete.
Because the front and rear panel lines have some gaps,
we will use the
3D model to make them smoother.
Adjust the size of the seat.
After adjusting the size, we still need to re-sew the panel line.
Next, come to the part of the sleeve.
We will make a new panel line.
After we select the panel line,
set up the inner lining.
Make it neat and warm.
Make it a small sleeve.
To add inner lining for clothing,
when making double-layer clothing,
there will be more details to be set up.
We can align the excess inner line to the inner lining of the panel line.
We can add the inner lining of the panel line.
In the chest area
and the back of the back of the panel,
add the inner lining.
This area is mainly used to make the outer lining of the coat.
After selecting the clothing panel,
make it to the inside.
Then, remove the joint.
Then, reset the joint relationship between the panel lines.
In the same way, we will roll the clothing to the exterior, and after removing the link, we will set the link again.
We put the clothing on the outside again, and after removing the connection, we set the connection again.
Delete the sleeve panel, select the inner line.
After cutting the panel, we only keep the outer part, and delete the rest.
Adjust the position of the panel in the 2D window.
Due to the cut panel, the previous sewing line information will disappear.
We need to review it again.
Come to the bottom of the clothing.
In the back part, we can adjust its sewing line to make a gap effect.
The seam allowance is also adjusted.
Next, we will make a sleeve panel for the sleeve paper.
Arrange the panel around the model.
Then add a line on the panel with the tool of the plus button.
We can use the modern sewing tool directly to add a line at the place where we just added a point.
After we select these two lines, we set up a label line to cancel the extension of the hook line, and we can directly set up two normal labels and merge them together.
Next, set up a label line.
This label line is mainly used for positioning.
After that, I will delete it.
After the positioning is complete, we can use the twist tool to add a twist and add a buckle.
We can use the edge twist tool to adjust the position and angle of the buckle, and then use the thin twist tool to tighten the buckle.
Before the simulation, we need to set up the level for the outer plate and then freeze the inner plate, so that it will be more stable during the simulation process.
We will also freeze the outer clothing, and only let the sleeve part participate in the simulation.
You can see that the sleeve and the sleeve have a gap.
We will activate the buckle first, so that the buckle will not participate in the simulation.
Because we want to set up the level for the sleeve,
we need to set up the level for the sleeve and then freeze the outer plate.
In order to set up the level for the sleeve, the level of the sleeve needs to be higher than the level of the sleeve.
The current sleeve level is 1, and the sleeve level is 2.
It can automatically set up the outer plate.
Then I will modify the inner part of the sewing line to change it to TURN.
Use the edge twist tool.
After activating the TURN, adjust the position of the TURN.
Then do the simulation again.
After selecting the sleeve plate, you can align it to the other side.
Then arrange it in the right position and then do the simulation.
Since we do not align the sleeve plate,
we need to adjust the sleeve plate.
So here we need to add the TURN again for it.
We can select the TURN tool and add the TURN directly in the 3D window.
In this part, the TURN has a gap.
We need to arrange the TURN in the right position and then do the simulation.
In the 3D window, select the sleeve plate.
Then clear their level.
This can avoid conflicts with unnecessary sleeve plates in the subsequent simulation process.
You need to remember that every time you finish the costume and set the level,
you need to reset its level to 0.
Use the TURN tool to add the TURN.
Then, the TURN point will be removed.
Use the TURN tool to add the TURN to the sleeve plate.
Then, delete the TURN.
Make the sleeve plate straight.
Select the difference between the plate and sleeve.
On the sides, align the sleeve plates.
Select the inner line and apply a angle smaller than 180 degrees for it to have a folding effect.
After selecting the loop, turn off the conflict in the attribute editor.
This can prevent the loop from conflicting and make the simulation more stable.
We can adjust the size of the button and the eye.
Next, I will make the belt for D1.
Before making the belt, I will select the D100 version external cable.
Set a 6-pin pin.
Add the inner line to the waist.
In the 3D window, we can observe that this inner line is not aligned.
We need to adjust the position of the inner line on the panel to make them align in the 3D window.
Align the inner line to the outer line of the panel.
In the uniquely small monitor layout, as shown in the upper-right box.
After the inner line aligns, add a new Bind.
We need to customize the waist of the belt.
In the lower-right box, ensure that the inner line is aligned in the 3D window.
After selecting the built-in internal line, you can paste it on the back panel and align the internal line to the external panel line, because we need to cut it afterwards.
If the internal line is not aligned to the external panel line, it may be cut wrong.
After aligning the internal line to the external panel line, we need to simulate it again to see if the internal line is aligned.
Use the multi-sided tool to draw the panel panel on the 2D window and set the internal line diameter.
Align it to the waistband.
Select the panel panel of the panel.
Paste it on the outside, and paste it on the outside of the internal line.
Since the panel is too large in diameter, we need to simulate its diameter first to make it smoother.
After making a side, we can align the panel panel with the internal line, align it to the other side.
Then paste it again.
Paste the panel panel to the back panel line.
After selecting the panel panel, align the panel panel to the outside.
Select the panel panel of the waistband.
Cut the panel panel to the waistband.
Delete the other panels.
Select the straight point on the panel panel to arrange them neatly.
Delete the extra internal line information on the panel panel.
möglich的内部线信息
After seamstress.
After sewing, you can choose the sewing line to combine them.
Choose the belt plate and activate the center point.
After activating the center point, we can use the center point as the axis to release the plate.
By using this method to make a belt, we can avoid the process of wearing a belt during the simulation process.
The belt made in this way is directly attached to the outer side of the suit.
Because we have adjusted the size of the belt just now, we still need to adjust its sewing line.
We can use the panel line expansion.
Extend the belt.
When I simulate the belt, I use the default fabric to simulate.
The default fabric is more stable than other fabrics.
Use hardening to eliminate the wrinkle.
Extend the belt plate again.
Use the round and smooth curve tool to add a round angle to the belt.
Delet the curve point of the round angle.
We can adjust the size of the angle.
Activate all the panels.
Simulate the whole thing.
See if it is stable.
Choose the inner plate and apply 100 of the elasticity to maintain the size of the original board.
Select the outer layer and increase the resolution.
The inner layer is small and the outer layer is large.
This way, you can create a lot of details on the outer layer.
We can see that the
We can add a fixed point by pressing the W key and then moving the position of the fixed point and fixing it.
On the other side, we can also use the same method to fix it.
In addition to using a fixed point, you can also use a fake tool to fix it.
We can also use a fake tool to fix it.
We need to adjust the seam line of the outer layer and the inner layer.
We should sew the outer layer together.
The seam line is sewn on the clothes because the outer layer is obtained through the Cron version.
Next, we will make a backpack from a new project file.
First, we will make a rectangular version and arrange it on the back of the virtual model.
We will use the Cron version to the outside and adjust the seam line between them.
Measure the width of the rectangular version.
Then use the rectangular tool to click on the 2D window to make a rectangular version.
Use a free sewing tool to sew it.
When sewing, the double-sided straight line can be sewn directly on the board.
Use a long strip of paper and add the paper to the side.
In order to avoid affecting the thickness of the backpack,
We will sew the front and back of the two pieces of paper.
and then simulate it.
Turn on the virtual model.
Use the internal multidirectional tool,
add the internal line,
and then remove the interlocking relationship of the board.
To remove the interlocking relationship,
when editing a piece of board,
the other piece of board will not be affected.
Re-column the board to the outside.
At the same time, to remove the interlocking relationship,
select the internal line,
cut it off,
and then adjust the position of the board in the 3D window
to make the second back.
Select the board outline,
and use the board outline expansion to expand the board.
When using the board outline expansion,
we can also choose
whether to create an internal line.
Use the free sewing tool
to sew the board.
Because there is no need
to make a foldable back,
remove the internal line first.
Re-column the board to the outside.
To make the back cover,
the same,
remove the interlocking relationship,
select the internal line,
cut the board,
and remove the extra part.
Then re-sew it.
At the same time,
we need to change its sewing line type
to Turned.
After we have done the center point,
we can adjust the board
by using the center point as the axis.
After the board is sewn,
we still need to adjust its sewing line
to avoid the board being stretched.
Then,
use the round-shape curve tool
to add the round corner.
In the horizontal,
we can enter the exact number,
and also lock the length of the line.
For the board,
add the inner line.
After adding the inner line,
the double-layer effect will be more rich.
Use the inner rectangle tool
to add the inner shape on the board
to create the effect of
a magic sticker.
Then,
paste the built-in inner line
on the backpack.
Then,
adjust the position of the inner line
to the center,
and sew them together.
Then,
adjust the position of the inner line
to the center,
and sew them together.
Once again,
re-sew the board
and remove the extra part.
If you re-sew the board,
the outer board
will not have the effect of
mixing.
After selecting the inner line,
cut off the excess inner line.
I added two inner lines
to the cut-off part
of the two boards.
Then,
adjust the position
of the inner lines.
If you re-sew the inner lines
and make them wider
than 180 degrees,
it will be not slanted.
If you select the outer line
and make it shorter than 180 degrees,
it will be slanted.
Then,
adjust the position
at the center
and fold it hatwards.
Then,
Next, I will continue to make pockets for backpacks.
Use the built-in multidirectional tool to draw lines.
When drawing, click the right-click button.
We can also set the mirror in the spring window.
Here I use the plus point branch tool.
After adding a straight line at the bottom of the panel,
use the position function to continue drawing lines.
This can ensure that the built-in pattern is symmetrical.
Then I use the round-shape curve tool to add round corners to the backpacks.
This makes the surroundings of the backpacks more round.
Choose the right line section and the outline of the panel.
Then use the hook tool to hook the panel.
When using the hook tool to hook the panel,
the pattern you choose needs to be closed.
The pattern you choose needs to be closed.
Then you can successfully hook the panel.
The part of making small pockets is the same as the part of making the second layer of backpacks.
Here I will speed up.
So before I hook the backpacks, I will narrow and then Можно container in the middle.
You can see that the backpacks can be connected in the small messages under the backpacks.
This again requires the pattern submission.
Then we quickly go to the front upsetting sides and contact hairs at the bottom.
Here, the pattern is in this void.
The pattern can be added continuously.
Then you can also see the divide point.
Next I will link with the straight line.
Next, I will make a large cover.
Use a multi-sided tool.
Click and hold the right button to open the mirror.
Let's arrange the board on the backpack.
After choosing the board, turn it over.
Make its hair line outwards.
Adjust the board shape.
Then use the multi-sided tool.
Add a middle point to the middle part of the backpack.
Use the free sewing tool to sew along the middle point to both sides.
This can ensure that the cover of the sewing is in the center of the board.
Adjust the curve of the cover and adjust the board shape.
Then adjust the curve of the cover and adjust the board shape.
After choosing the board shape, we can insert the inner line of the inner line.
Then cut and sew.
This can have a sewing line effect in the 3D window.
The details will be more abundant.
Remove the left and right interlocking relationship.
Add the inner line on the cover and adjust its position.
Then use the multi-sided tool to make a long board.
Line up the boards as shown.
Adjust the direction of the hair line.
Use the sewing tool.
Sew along the inner line.
Then align the outer line of the blackboard of the two cars.
Adjust the curve of the inner line.
Align the inner line to the outer line of the blackboard.
Then add point.
Then again we choose short line and adjust the curve of the inner line.
Copy and paste this board, then cut it.
After deleting the excess part, we re-shape the shape of the left-side line.
Then sew the top and bottom two boards together.
Use the inner rectangle tool to make the inner shape of the inner side.
Copy and paste the inner shape of the inner side.
After selecting the inner shape of the inner side, activate the center point.
You can use the center point as the axis for the inner shape of the inner side.
Then use the plus point division tool to click the right button on the inner line.
We can set it to the length division in the spring.
Then sew the inner shape of the inner side and the long strip board.
We can adjust the length of the strip board and keep tightening the belt cover.
Use the hook tool to hook the inner shape of the inner side into the strip board.
Then sew it together.
After sewing it together, we can add it to the outside.
We can see that there is a gap in the strip board.
This is due to the direction of the sewing line.
When sewing, make sure that the direction of the sewing is the same.
After sewing, re-shape it again to solve the problem of the gap.
Use the same method to make the two inner strips below.
Cut them into strips and sew them together.
When sewing, pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
It needs to be the same.
In this part, I measured the distance between the two inner strips.
And then I made a long strip.
And sew them together.
Choose a strip with a rough outline.
And sew it to the end of the inner strip.
On the cut out strip, also sew it to the end of the inner strip.
And then the other strip will be sewn together.
Seek the inner strip on the inside.
And apply the angle of 180 degrees to the fold.
Use the angle of 180 degrees to the fold.
Seek the outer strip, and apply the angle of 180 degrees to the fold.
There will be obvious fold marks around the join tip line.
Seek the edge strips, and cut the end out.
And fold it to the outside.
After the layer is frozen, we will simulate it again.
The difference occurs due to the size of the particle diameter of the layer.
We need to reduce the particle diameter of the layer and the impact thickness.
After the layer is frozen, we will simulate it again to solve the problem we just solved.
To the side of the backpack, use the 3D drawing tool to draw a line on the backpack.
We can position the line according to the position of the 2D window.
Then use the internal multidirectional tool to draw a line.
After drawing, we can delete the line in the 3D window.
Then we can make a fake zipper.
Before making the zipper, I choose the external line of the panel and set the border of the internal line.
Then align it to the internal line of the panel.
We can choose the internal line, then use the collocation tool to collocate them into panels.
Then use the free-for-all tool to sew them together.
After we select the panel, we can add it to the outer part of the panel.
After adding it to the outer part of the panel, we will simulate it again.
I want to change the opening direction of the panel here.
After I delete one side of the seam line, I sew the other side again.
Then we can use the free-for-all tool to sew the opening of the 2 sides.
The freedom of sewing is also displayed.
After selecting the board and the inner line, we can double-click to activate the center point.
Use the center point as the center point to set the board and the inner line.
We can also adjust the overall position of it.
If there is a gap in the board, we can add it to the outside.
I will make a pocket for it on the side of the backpack.
The method of making a pocket here is the same as before.
I will speed up appropriately.
I added a straight line at the center of the pocket.
Then I use the round-shape curve tool to click the straight line and drag it out to make a semicircle.
Then double-click to select this inner line and carve it into a board and then sew them together.
After selecting the board, add it to the outside.
Copy a board and then sew it with the inner line.
We can adjust the size of the board.
After selecting the straight line, use the edit point line tool to activate the center point.
Use the center point as the axis to adjust the size and then delete the straight line.
Then add a curve.
After selecting the square, click on the board in the window and add the square.
After selecting the square, right-click and we can set the function of sewing for the square.
After setting the function of sewing, we can sew the inner board.
In the letter editor, we can modify the shape and size of the square.
Use the inner square tool to click the board.
Using the inner square tool to click on the board.
In the popup table, we can set its length and width.
After缠憸内部模型上裕模型上裕模式上裕模式上裕模式上裕模式上裕模式上裕模式上裕模式上下裕模式上裕模式上裕模式上裕模式 around裕模 passed to былathnie
After melting things in the map, we can fit it into a board and continue to use the inner square tool to Powertrain.
We can notice that the sewing line is intersected.
We need to turn the panels horizontally first, so that they are aligned with the direction of the hair line, and then we can process them.
Continue to use the internal multidirectional tool to draw the internal shape on the backpack.
In this position, I will make an electronic-like internal shape for the backpack.
Use the round-shape curve tool to add the angle.
After the drawing is completed, we use the
hook tool to hook it into the panel.
Then, we return to the backpack to apply a softer fabric.
We use the Cotton Box Fold here.
But you can notice that there is an imbalance in the part of the cover.
We need to set the level of the outer cover.
Then, we can adjust the level of the outer cover.
We can adjust the level of the outer cover.
Finally, arrange the position of the inner easily.
Then, we will proceed to modeling.
After arranging, we move on to suffering.
Adjust the planes of interior.
Adjusting the areas of inner pattern,
adjust the contents of the easiestritial 2.
Adjusting the positions of internal mäaw ouais,
and adjust the length.
In this way, we can enjo the transparent lining of the cover.
Let's open the costume project file, and then only import the backpack version.
We can adjust the position of the backpack in the 3D window.
Freeze the costume version.
Let's make a backpack in this window.
We will make a backpack version in the 2D window.
Arrange it on the shoulder of the virtual model.
After selecting the version outline, use the length to narrow the bottom a little.
Then we can use the tool to edit the curve.
Click on the version outline.
Add the curve point.
Use the tool to add the curve line on the backpack.
After that, we will make a double-layer backpack.
To make the double layer effect, add the curve line.
There will be more details.
Then use the tool to create a straight line on the backpack.
This straight line is mainly used to locate.
We use the tool to click on the right button on the line.
We can set the position of the point.
Then I will use the free movement tool.
Start sewing from the point just added.
You can see that the direction of the sewing line is now crossed.
The same is because the direction of the line is different.
We need to level turn the board.
After making them find the same direction and solving the problem of the cross-section of the sewing line,
then simulate.
Align with the belt of the board.
Then put it in the position of the additional point on the other side.
Adjust the position of the board in the 3D window.
If you want to turn it in the direction of the line and keep the sewing line not crossed,
you can select the board and right-click to turn it over.
At the beginning of making the board, I usually give it a harder leather fabric.
This can prevent it from having a thin spine.
Then I will adjust its shape.
Before simulation, let's use the back of the bag.
We can reverse-activate the boards that are not in conflict with the simulation.
Frozen and reverse-activated boards can optimize the scene to a certain extent.
Increase the speed of the simulation.
Because the gap between the belts is too small,
I will adjust the position of the sewing line.
Make them wider.
Adjust the position of the backpack in the 3D window.
Let the belt part fit in the shoulder of the model.
After selecting the 10 version, you can turn it back on first.
This makes it more convenient for us to adjust the position of the belt.
To make the belt not go up,
we need to adjust the sewing line of the belt to Turned.
After we freeze it,
we continue to make the belt below.
Use the rectangle tool to gather a piece of small board.
Similarly, I will use the plus point division tool to add a straight line point on the backpack.
This allows me to determine the position of the belt that needs to be sewn.
Then I will adjust the board.
Use the change length tool to widen one side.
We only need to adjust the side of the board.
Then add a line.
After cutting,
leave one side and turn it.
Then we can use the free sewing tool
to sew to the position of the just added point.
Align the board to the other side
and sew it up at the same time.
That's it.
Now we need to make the strap.
Use the rectangle tool to gather a piece of long strip.
Adjust the position of the strap to the 3D window.
Then we can sew the strap to other places in the
back of the bag.
If we need to make a strap,
we can use this tool.
We can set the hexagonal diameter in this part and then copy and paste the board, adjust its 3D position, and set the hexagonal diameter again, and then sew them together.
We can use the extension or shortening of this board to tighten the belt.
Let's copy a small board again. This board is used to connect two belts.
I need to adjust the length of the two ends of this board and the length of the two belts above and below to the same length.
Here I use the adjustment tool to adjust the length.
When their lengths are unified, we can use the line sewing tool to sew them together.
I also sew the length of the two ends of the two belts above and below to the same length.
we can adjust the length of the two belts above and below to match the length of the two belts above and below.
Then I sew some rib lines for this board to create a double-layer effect.
Thread the board to the outside.
Through shortening of the bottom boards, we can tighten the belts simply.
Since we need to align the panels, we need to remove the connection relationship of the original panels first, then we can align them.
Activate the back panel and insert it into the simulation.
Adjust the length of the panel to tighten the back panel.
Select the back panel and activate it, but keep the most built-in panel frozen.
This can stabilize the 3D position of the back more stably.
Now we need to activate the 1.0 panel.
Then the frozen back panel.
Adjust the connection relationship between the 1.0 and the back panel.
After the adjustment, we activate the 1.0 panel and the back panel.
Try to see if the simulation is stable.
Reduce the thickness of the back panel.
Activate the back panel.
Add the organization
Freeze the most static panels
in the whole modeling.
In this way the leather bag will naturally go down smoothly.
When the meuder creation is complete, innovated all the multimedia indemnificationens this podemos mod động所有衣服
momento color
check to see if there is a position that is unstable.
We just want to cancel the installation The
image can be edited with the program.
First, we should modify the display.
We can adjust this pattern operation.
We can also change the height of the arrangement board.
We can adjust the arrangement board position using the locator in the 3D window.
On the right, we can add an arrangement point.
Then we can apply the arrangement point to the arrangement board just added.
We can also adjust the arrangement point on the arrangement board position.
I will make a rolled-up board at the bottom of the bag.
Before making, we can reactivate all the boards and hide them.
We will make a long strip board.
Because the direction of the board is curved along the X-axis,
we need to make the board longer along the X-axis.
This way, the arrangement board will naturally be rolled up.
When we roll the board,
we need to properly increase the thickness of the board and the thickness of the material.
This can make the board more stable during the modeling process.
After making a small board,
click on Arrange Point.
After arranging the board, make it hold the large board.
Use the linear rolling tool to roll up both sides.
Then freeze the large board.
Activate the small board.
Apply the arrangement point for the small board.
Let it be simulated to the outermost layer.
I applied a leather material for the small board.
Then simulate.
After simulation, we will find that the board is now too long.
After we rearrange the position,
adjust the length of the board.
Make the small board completely wrapped with the large board.
Let the board be folded.
The rolled board should be wool.
So I will change the original leather material to wool.
After changing, we need to re-apply the thickness for it.
Then we add again the thickness of the big board.
Then simulate.
Activate the smaller board.
Let's simulate.
The smaller board is more natural.
To prevent the board from falling down during the simulation.
In the 3D window, right click on the simulation element.
Adjust the thickness to 0.
After unfreezing the larger board.
To make the smaller board tighter.
I will choose to decrease the final length.
Activate the larger board.
Let's simulate.
Reduce the thickness of the board.
to make it have more grid.
In this part, I will make the small panel wider.
After selecting the small panel,
activate the center point,
and then widen the panel.
Select the outline of the two-end panel,
and then set the border of the line.
Cut and sew the inner line.
I will sew a fabric,
and then apply it to the middle panel.
After that,
I will change it to a transparent fabric.
Now we can show the back of the panel,
and then adjust,
and then adjust the panel above
in the position of the 3D window.
Press and hold to confirm whether the panel is intersecting.
After activating the small panel,
we can use the fix tool
to fix it.
Press and hold to confirm whether the panel is intersecting.
Then we select the fabric of the middle panel,
and change its transparency to 0.
So in the 3D window,
the panel can exist in a transparent form.
In the vertical display menu,
we can hide or display the fixed needle.
Press and hold to confirm whether the panel is intersecting.
We can increase the thickness of the two panels,
to make it look more real.
Press and hold to confirm whether the panel is intersecting.
Then I will add the belt buckle to the backpack.
Before adding,
we need to sew two lab lines on the panel,
and then sew a small panel
to sew it on the lab line
and add it to the outside.
The gap between the panels
is because the thickness of the contact between the panels is not enough.
We need to increase its contact thickness
and the thickness of the panel.
Then we lengthen this panel
so that there is a gap between them.
Reduce the particle diameter
to make the transition smoother.
In the sketch,
add the belt buckle to the scene
and stick the glue tool on the panel.
We can click on
the play function in the upper right corner
to play the object,
then adjust its size and position.
We can also shrink the middle panel a little.
The other side is the same.
I will skip this step.
After activating all panels,
we can visualize the whole model
to see if it is stable.
At the same time,
the layers of all panels in the vacuum
are set to 0,
to avoid any interference
in the subsequent simulation process.
Now, let's make a cross-package for the virtual model.
First, activate the inner panel
and the backpack panel.
After creating a long panel,
place it on the shoulder of the virtual model.
Since we have turned off the gravity
in the simulation property before,
we need to open the simulation property
and set the gravity to negative 9800.
Then, the panel will naturally drop when simulated.
Press the W key, click on the panel,
we can add a fixed pin.
In the simulation process,
we can take out the fixed pin
and adjust the position of the panel.
I used a new fabric for the panel
and modified its name.
By adjusting the position of the fixed pin,
we can control the position of the backpack.
Since the backpack is too short,
I can lengthen the backpack appropriately.
Press the W key,
when we ring,
we can춰 the fixed pin.
To adjust the position of the backpack,
We can add a fixed pin
Similarly, we can apply a harder wool fabric for the belt, and we can eliminate the fragility of the fabric.
After pasting and pasting, the panel is rearranged around the virtual model.
Then we can select the right panel and clear the fixations on the panel.
We can adjust the length of the panel, and then adjust its position in the 3D window.
To ensure that the direction of the hair line is the same, here I open the black and white surface mode, and then merge it with another panel.
We can use the shrink or lengthen panel to shrink the whole belt.
After selecting the panel, we can rotate it in the direction of the 2D window.
This allows me to make small bags on the belt.
After selecting the panel outline, we can expand the panel outline.
In the panel, we can enter the value.
The value of the value is the vertical line generated by the expansion of the panel outline.
We can adjust the panel line on the upper side of the frozen panel, and then rotate it in the simulation process to adjust the bottom panel.
After hardening the panel, we can quickly eliminate the fragility of the hair.
After creating the shape of the panel, we can remove the hardening.
Select the panel outline on both sides, and then we can set the number of the panel lines.
After setting the number of the panel lines, I think the panel is a bit too short.
After selecting the panel outline, I will extend the panel again.
After the panel outline, we can change the length of the panel.
For example, if I want to make the panel longer, I can cut the panel length to a certain width.
We can make the panel line longer.
If we want to make the panel longer, we can adjust the volume of the panel.
In this section, only one of the panels is kept.
We will make a small package using this panel.
In this section, the same thing is used to expand the panel line.
Expand the panel line, and then expand it to generate the inner line.
Then use the fold and fold tool.
Apply the fold angle to it.
I can change the angle of the fold in the panel line.
Fold it up and then heat it up.
After the panel line is hardened, the effect of the fold will be more obvious.
In order to make the simulation more realistic,
I will first move the back panel.
Then drag the back panel in the simulation process.
In order to make the fold effect more obvious,
we can apply a harder fabric to the backpack.
Here I use the leather fabric.
Then we can change the vertical angle of the panel line.
Let it stand up.
After activating the back panel,
we can apply a harder fabric to the panel line.
We need to change the inner line of the panel line between the small package and the back panel.
Change the inner line of the panel line to Turn.
Then we can see that the small package is completely straight.
Next, we can make the back panel.
After we make a piece of the panel line,
cut it.
Then use the line and red line tool to red line it with the back panel.
At the same time, we can modify the model line type.
To ensure that the simulation is more stable,
we can first freeze the panel line and the small package panel lines.
Next, we can adjust the position of the panel line on the panel.
After choosing the panel line,
we can set the inner line of the panel line.
We can adjust the position of the panel line on the panel.
At this position,
we need to reduce the vertical angle of the panel,
so that it has more grid.
Adjust the inner line to the appropriate position.
We can set the vertical angle of the panel line,
so that it can be folded 90 degrees.
To shorten the length of the panel line,
use the inner rectangle tool to click the panel line.
Create an inner pattern.
Then copy and paste it to the panel line of the small package.
Mix them together as a model.
We can paste the remaining panels by copying and pasting.
Then we can paste the remaining panels by copying and pasting.
After mixing them together,
remember to change the model line type of the panel line.
Change the model line type to Turn.
The rest of the parts will be accelerated appropriately.
Before I change the position,
I will use the
changing tool.
I fixed the backpack's submerged area.
Before I change the position in dish Overwatch,
I shifted a pinch
To prevent the electron from being affected, we can freeze the part of the electron first.
Let's hope that it is OK.
Let's open a new project file and import a product model.
Let's import a product model from here.
Then we open a new project file and import a product model.
In the icon,
We can change the model's position to a vertical position.
Then, Shift-X can show the frame of the model.
Then we can click on the frame above to adjust the model's position.
After adjusting the model's position, we can select the model we just saved.
We can save it as a position file.
After saving, we can search for the position file we just saved.
After we find the position file we just adjusted, we can double-click to change the model's position.
After we find the position file, we can enter the position of the model.
We can check whether the electronic part is same with the backpack.
We can click on the fix icon to adjust the initial position.
Thank you.
In the last part, we will show the surface mode of the domain, show the thickness of the board, and then adjust the conflict thickness and historical interval of the board.